My name is Nkoyo Udo from Akwa Ibom State (Nigeria).
The person next to me is my sister and her baby.
Mrs Nkoyo Udo & Family
Akwa Ibom, Nigeria
This one next to her is her in-law. This is my sister. This is my sister and her husband.
Mrs Nkoyo Udo & Family
Akwa Ibom, Nigeria
We are here to share a wonderful testimony to the glory of God.
It all started November 2017
when my sister went to the hospital for delivery.
When she went, the doctor tested her and told her that she would not be able to deliver
without an operation.
And immediately the doctor made mention of operation, we were scared
because of what was involved.
And immediately my sister called me, I rushed down from the office to the hospital.
I told the doctor that he should wait. That he should let me seek the face of God first.
I picked up my phone. I called the prayer line.
That this was what was happening. The person at the prayer line told me, "No problem.
That in every situation God is saying something.
That nothing will happen to my sister and the baby".
I had faith in these words.
And we tried.
We couldn't succeed normally like that and later resolved on having the operation.
My sister still underwent an operation.
Before the operation, the doctor told me that they were trying inside to see
how they could remove the baby but it was not possible. They had to use forceps.
When they were using the forceps, due to mismanagement, the baby got injured.
As it was a private hospital, they didn't have the equipment to treat the baby.
The doctor then transferred my sister and the baby to the General Hospital.
When they went there, the situation became worse.
They first asked, "What happened to the baby before they transferred the baby to the hospital?"
The baby got injured as you can see on the picture that has been placed here.
The baby got injured.
This is the picture of the baby on the screen of the televisión.
And you can even see right there the baby's brain, which was very, very dangerous.
When I asked the doctor, "What are we going to do now at the hospital?",
the doctor told me, "I have not seen such a case before.
That we need to try; in this situation, it is 50/50".
I was shocked. I didn't know what to do at that particular moment.
I told my sister, "What I want to do is that ... I believe in the God of T.B. Joshua.
He will never disappoint me.
Being a member here and also a partner, that stepping my feet here at the arena of Liberty,
that indeed, I will come back with a testimony".
And I came here.
When I came here in November 2017, I was opportune to be placed in the prayer line.
When I was in the prayer line, the man of God prayed for me.
At that time, I used this picture you saw on the board as the medium of contact
because I couldn't bring my sister and the baby down to The SCOAN.
When the man of God was praying for me, I believed in my mind,
"Definitely, he is praying for my sister right there at the hospital".
I was also opportune to be given the New Morning Water.
I rushed down to the hospital when I went back to my state, Akwa Ibom.
I administered the New Morning Water on the baby on the first day and the mother.
With regard to the mother, after the operation, the wound refused to close.
The doctor told me, "We tried. It didn´t close. We are going to stitch her again".
I said, "No, doctor! It will be very painful and you should not do that".
My sister was still crying and I said, "What am I going to do?"
I told my sister, "Just calm down. When I come back from where I want to go,
definitely you will have a testimony".
When I returned from The SCOAN, I put a demand on the annointing in this place.
Because my papa, my mentor T.B. Joshua, usually says that in every situation God is still saying something
and our situation is not like that of others. These words motivated me.
I rushed from Akwa Ibom State down here and was privileged to get the New Morning Water.
I administered that New Morning Water on the baby and my sister.
Surprisingly - tell your neighbour, "Surprisingly" -
the wound began to close, close, close, close.
This was something the doctor told me before I left,
"My sister, I don't think it will be possible for the next eight months
for this baby to be here in the hospital".
I then asked, "What happened? How are we going to get the money
because drugs there on a daily basis - you buy one for 10.000, 15.000, 7.000 -
before we knew it, all that we had got exhausted.
We didn't have money again. I said, "Ok, this last money that is remaining,
let me rush down to The SCOAN".
So when the wound started closing, brethren, I was surprised.
After four days...
Hallelujah! We can see on the screen the same spot where the baby was injured
and the sore was widening and widening until the sister came to The SCOAN
with a picture of the mother and the baby and interceded on their behalf,
received prayer from the man of God and got the New Morning Water.
She went back to meet the baby and the mother in the hospital,
ministered the New Morning Water and the wound that was so wide and so deep that you could see the brain
of the little baby started closing up and that is the result we can see today.
It is completely healed. Shall we put our hands together beautifully for Jesus!
As there was not enough blood in my sister, they stored the fibroid when they did the operation.
They couldn't remove the fibroid because of the blood.
And at that particular time there was no blood to transfuse.
And the fibroid was still there. After three days, my sister began to swell up everywhere -
I was shocked! I said, "How can I lose two people at the same time! God forbid such a bad thing!
I cannot serve a living God and be disappointed". I was crying.
I was praying. I was meditating and indeed God of T.B. Joshua that I serve did wonders!
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
After three days of ministration of the New Morning Wáter, I had a dream.
The man of God appeared to me in my dream
and told me that he was just coming for me and the baby alone, not for any other person;
that I should rush to the hospital and bring the baby.
I did. I rushed down and brought the baby to him.
I didn't even know what the man of God put on the baby's head at that spot
but I saw his hand like this on the spot.
When I saw the hand, the man of God prayed for the baby and said, "Take the baby.
She is free. She is healed".
Mrs Nkoyo Udo & Family
Akwa Ibom, Nigeria
The baby I'm talking about is not far away -
she's here, right here in our midst.
Immediately after the dream, after one week, the wound closed totally.
Hallelujah!
At the earlier stage, before I came to The SCOAN, the doctor told me
that they had not seen such a case before, the wound was too wide,
the baby's brain had opened and they couldn't do anything
but they were going to do what they could - medically.
When the doctor came out and told me that, I told him
that I believe that the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua is still saying something
and definitely, He will still say something.
So when I went back and administered the New Morning Water,
and the doctor saw that the wound was completely closed, he was surprised.
One of the nurses that saw when I administered the New Morning Water on the baby asked me,
"Madam, I saw you holding something in your hand. What was that?"
I told her, "Madam, do you care to know what I was holding in my hand that day?"
She said, "Yes, because I have not seen this kind of thing before.
This wound is not even up to two months and the baby is completely healed!"
I told the doctor that it was the New Morning Water from The SCOAN; where I belong.
And today, this is my sister and this is the baby.
They are completely healed to the glory of God!
Amen. Thank You, Jesus! Let´s clap for Jesus one more time!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I am Inobo Akban and the baby I'm carrying is my daughter, Destiny Akban.
I´m from Akwa Ibom State (Nigeria).
My sister has said it all!
I was the one that was in pain. I was sick. I didn't know anything.
Even the hospital that they transferred my daughter to, it was my mother that stayed with my daughter
at that hospital for four days before the doctor told me to go and stay with my daughter at the hospital.
When my sister came back from The SCOAN, that was when I knew that I am a living soul.
Now I feel very happy!
I'm glad that my baby is alive. I am alive.
When I saw the wound at the Teaching Hospital, I was crying all through.
When my health was bad, when I was down, I was even asking God, "Why?
Why this pain for a baby that is just coming into the world and that has not done anything,
that does not not know anything?"
But God was still consoling me.
My sister tried her best as a sister to rush down to meet the man of God.
The head that I was unable to touch at that time, now I can touch that place.
I can touch my baby's head.
Everywhere was soft. It was only this place that was strong on this head.
But now everywhere is strong. Praise the Lord! Emmanuel!
Put your hands together for Jesus Christ!
Thank you!
My advice to the whole world and the people that are seated here
is that when you have a problem, when you are terrified,
don't run to satan, don't run to a witch doctor,
run to God because God is the Author and the Finisher of everything.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Thank you!
So, let's just hear a word or two from a brother here.
Tell us your name and who is the woman to you?
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ennis Akban.in-law.
The woman here by my side is my sister-in-law - the wife of my elder brother.
I'm here to thank God for what God has done for our family
because what no man can do is very possible before God
and He has all the ability to change things.
We are so amazed and so surprised to see this kind of thing happen.
That's why we all came as a family to thank God.
I want to thank God for Prophet T.B. Joshua.
We had been hearing this name, and my sister kept on telling us to come.
We never thought it was this kind of thing.
I have seen proof and evidence; that's why I believe in Him.
The Bible says, "Believe God and you will succeed.
But when you believe the prophets, you shall prosper".
So that's why we all came because we now believe what we have seen.
I say, "May the Lord bless him".
And I want to advise everybody:
The devil only comes to intimidate you.
Don't allow whatever he brings your way to take you to a witch doctor
because you will lose direction.
Every problem coming to you, God wants you to take that problem to Him
because He has something to do in your life. Blessed be the name of the Lord!
Put your hands together for Jesús!
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Finally, sister, what is your word of advice?
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My advice first goes to the people who are still yet to partner with EmmanuelTV.
I want to advise you that you should not delay anymore.
Since I started partnering with this ministry, I have not been disappointed in life.
I have seen so many things happening to me -
breakthrough in my career, finances, in so many ways.
Then secondly, to the viewers all over the world
and to those that are seated right here in this auditorium.
I want to advise you that in every situation, God is still saying something;
that in God, there is no impossibility.
With God, everything is possible.
Any situation or challenge - because our Papa, T.B. Joshua, my mentor usually says
that it is not any other thing than a mere challenge.
Anything you came here with today,
believe that as you're going, you're going with a testimony.
Thank you. Put your hands together for Jesus!
We want to congratulate the baby's mother and the baby
for the wonderful healing that has taken place in the life of this child.
We also want to encourage you to remember that you were healed by the grace of God through His Word.
So make His Word the standard for your life
and also train up this child in the way of the Lord so that when she grows up, she will not depart from it.
Remember, for God Almighty to save the life of this child,
it means that God has a purpose for her life.
We pray that God Almighty will give you the inner grace to train her up in the way of the Lord, in Jesus' name.
Once again, let´s clap for Jesus!
RV: Mel Flowers 07/04/2019